Guide to the Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks, 1850s-2000s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University, Durham, N.C., USA
- American Cookbooks 1980s, 13
  - It's Better Made with Butterfinger Candy Bars, 1985 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0036)
    Product: Butterfinger candy bar
  - Oreo Cookies Recipe & Party Booklet, 1982 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0037)
    Product: Oreo
  - Candy Making for Beginners, 1982 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0038)
    Product: Wilton CandyMaker supplies
  - Pillsbury Frosting Sweet and Easy, circa 1980 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0039)
    Product: cake mix and frosting
  - Baker's book of chocolate riches, 1985 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0040)
  - Hershey's Chocolate Recipe Collection: A Selection of Recipes from the Hershey Kitchens, 1989 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0041)
    Product: Hershey's chocolate products
  - You Can Bake Chocolate Desserts, Compliments of Nestle, 1983 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0042)
    Product: Nestlé's chocolate products: Toll House Morsels, Choco-Bake
  - Sweet morsel delights, circa 1985 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0043)
    Product: Nestlé's semi-sweet, butterscotch and milk chocolate morsels
  - A.1 International Steakburgers, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0044)
  - New Ways with Good Seasons Salad Dressing Mixes – Salads, Dips, Marinades, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0045)
    Product: Good Seasons Salad Dressing Mixes
  - Ketchup Recipe Collection, 1988 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0046)
  - Pickling Book, circa 1980 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0047)
    Product: Heinz vinegars
    Note: Tradition
  - Creative Cook's Secret: Worcestershire Recipes, 1984 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0048)
    Product: French's Worcestershire Sauce
  - Creative Cooking with Mr. Marinade, circa 1980 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0049)
    Product: Mr. Marinade
  - Easy Summer Living and Entertaining, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0050)
    Note: Aimed at women: recipes for 'busy days at the office or at home with the kids.' Weight: low calorie foods
  - Anchor Ovenware Microware Instructions and Recipes, circa 1980 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0052)
    Product: Anchor Ovenware microwave
    Note: Survey card inside, offer for Microwave Cooking Library
  - Microwave and Conventional Ovens: Helpful Hints, Use and Care, and our Favorite Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0053)
    Note: Color photographs, coupon and warranty registration card, picture and labels of accessories
  - Dual Purpose Microware Instructions and Recipes for Microwave and Conventional Ovens, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0054)
    Product: Microwave
    Note: Possibly the same as 1980sA-0030, color photographs, information on various racks, ad for Microwave Cooking Library
  - Microware Instructions and Recipes from Anchor Hocking, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0055)
  - Microwave Popcorn Popper/Steamer/Roaster Instructions and Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0056)
    Product: Microwave Popcorn Popper
  - Any Oven Cookbook, 1981 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0057)
    Note: Microwave cooking, scientific explanation of why Saran wrap is better than other wraps.
  - Saran Wrap & Microwaves: the Inside Story, 1982 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0058)
    Company: Dow Consumer Products
  - Oriental Wok & Steamer Cookery, 1982 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0059)
    Company: Himark
    Product: Bamboo steamer
  - Adventures in Complete Meal Microwave Cooking, 1984 (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0060)
  - Microwave Recipes & Instructions, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-02, Item 1980s-0061)
    Product: Micro-Go-Round
  - Microwaving with Nordic Ware, 1983 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0062)
    Product: Nordic Ware microwave cookware
  - Unusual Old World and American Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0063)
  - Cooking tagliatelle. Discover lots of new and tasty recipes for making tagliatelle, taglioni and lasagne, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0064)
    Company: OMC-Marcato
    Product: Ampia Marcato tagliatelle maker
  - Microwave Bounty And Your Oven Team Up For Great Tasting Food!, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0065)
    Product: Bounty
  - How to Cook for 1 or 2 with Reynolds Consumer Products, 1980 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0066)
    Product: Reynolds Wrap, etc.
  - Perla Meyers Gerber Legendary Blades Cookbook, 1984 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0067)
    Company: International Kitchen, Inc.
    Product: Gerber Legendary Blades
    Note: Perla Meyers black-and-white photograph in back, black-and-white photograph of knives, black-and-white drawings of knives and gadgets, introduction
  - Preview of 'The Way Mama Cooked It': From the Makers of Reynolds Wrap, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0068)
    Note: Advertisement for larger cookbook. Racial content: African-American woman and son/grandson cooking together on cover. Cookbook compiled from 'a national Black cooking contest'
  - Holiday Helper Recipes, 1982 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0069)
    Product: Cut-Rite wax paper
  - Better Homes and Gardens 'Best You Can Bake' Chocolate Desserts, Compliments of Nestlé, 1987 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0070)
    Product: Wok
    Note: History of Toll House cookies
  - Beginners Guide to Cake Decorating, 1981 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0071)
    Product: Wilton cake decorating products (icing bags, tips, etc.)
    Note: picture of clown cake on cover
  - 30-Minute Meals, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0072)
    Product: Carnation non-fat dry milk
  - Eat Light Eat Right Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0073)
    Product: Carnation Instant Non-Fat Dry Milk
    Note: Weight, convenience
  - Say Cheese, 1981 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0074)
    Company: Giant Food, Inc.
  - Classic Egg Dishes, 1980 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0075)
    Company: Incredible Edible Egg
    Note: Instructions on how to follow recipes for successful egg cooking (such as how to separate, beat eggs, etc.)
  - Fresh Ideas From Velveeta: All Easy and Extra Cheesy, 1986 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0076)
    Note: Includes Tex-Mex cuisine
  - Good Ideas Keep Popping Up., 1981 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0077)
  - Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese Cookbook, 1981 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0078)
    Note: Tradition, history of cream cheese and company, illustrated.
  - Contemporary Lifestyle Recipes, 1982 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0079)
    Product: Land O' Lakes sweet cream butter
  - Diet For A Healthy Heart, 1988 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0080)
    Product: Fleischmann's Margarines and Egg Beaters
  - Calcium-Rich Recipes with Milk, 1986 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0081)
    Company: National Dairy Board
    Note: Health, nutrition
  - Ricotta Recipes from Polly-O: Wonderful Ideas for the Most Versatile Cheese, 1989 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0082)
    Product: Pollio cheeses
  - Simply Irresistible Desserts, 1987 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0083)
  - Swiss Cheese Cookery: Dishes to Delight Cheese Lovers, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0084)
  - Itinerant Ripe Olive: A Guide to the Use of California Ripe Olives, 1983 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0085)
    Company: California Olive Industry
    Note: Color illustrations.
  - California Summer Fruits Recipes, 1984 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0086)
    Company: California Tree Fruit Agreement
    Product: CA summer fruits--peaches, pears, nectarines, plums
    Note: Color photographs, some black-and-white drawings, introduction (ripening, peeling, pitting, etc.)
  - California Summer Fruits Recipe Collection: A Taste of the Rainbow, 1980 (Box 1980s-03, Item 1980s-0087)
    Product: California Tree Fruits
  - Discover Cherimoyas, 1986 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0088)
    Company: California Tropics Corp
    Product: Cherimoyas
    Note: Exotic fruit
  - Recipe Collection for Del Monte Pineapple Tidbits, 1981 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0089)
    Product: Del Monte Pineapple Tidbits
  - Recipe Collection for Del Monte Pineapple Tidbits, 1981 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0090)
    Note: Same as 1980s-0089
  - Kiwano, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0091)
    Company: S. E. Morris
    Product: Kiwano' brand horned melon
    Note: Exotic fruit: New Zealand product
  - Recipes with Olé, 1986 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0092)
    Company: Spanish Olives Recipes
    Product: Spanish olives
    Note: Health, flavor, appearance of food
  - SunMaid Cookbook, 1980 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0093)
  - Our Favorite Date Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0094)
    Product: Sunsweet dates
  - Washington Apples, 1988 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0095)
    Company: Growers of Washington State Apples
    Note: Pamphlet, color photographs of apples, color drawing on cover
  - Guide To The Original Health Food., circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0096)
    Company: Washington Apple Commission
    Product: Washington State Apples
  - Healthy Choices for People with Diabetes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0097)
  - Rice Cake Recipes, 1983 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0098)
    Company: Chico-San
    Product: Rice cakes
  - Rice Appetizing and Easy Recipes, 1989 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0099)
    Company: Effem Foods Ltd.
  - El Molino Cookbook, 1980 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0100)
    Product: El Molino active dry yeast, wheat germ, gluten flour, etc.
    Note: Health food. Information and history of many grains and seeds, including historical Native American usage, genetically engineered strains, etc.
  - Food & Good Health – Cereal: The No-Time-For-Breakfast Breakfast!, 1982 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0101)
  - Favorite Recipes with Minute Rice Fast Fabulous Meals, 1989 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0102)
    Product: Multiple, esp. Minute Rice
    Note: Color photographs, information on Minute Rice
  - Our favorite Granola Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0103)
    Company: Golden Harvest
    Product: Granola Cereals
  - Kellogg's Bran Idea Book, 1982 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0104)
    Product: Kellogg Bran Cereals
    Note: Color photographs, fiber information, Cooking with Kellogg's insert, Calorie-Fiber counter, coupons
  - Cooking with Kellogg's, 1981 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0105)
    Note: Poor condition: cover falling off
  - Kellogg's Fiber Diet Planner, 1981 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0106)
    Note: Health, weight: 'doctor recommended' diet plan
  - Triscuit Whole Wheat Wafers Microwave Snackbook, 1989 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0107)
    Product: Triscuit Whole Wheat Wafers
  - Try these New and Exciting Recipes with Nilla Wafers, 1983 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0108)
    Product: Nilla Wafers
  - Five Nilla wafers Variations for Banana Puddings, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0109)
    Note: Singe sheet
  - America Entertains at Home with Pasta: Quarter-of-an-Hour Menus, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0110)
    Company: National Macaroni Institute
    Product: Pasta
    Note: Efficiency and speed of preparation, microwaves
  - Poppin' Fresh Yeast Bread Mix Fancy Recipes, 1984 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0111)
    Product: Poppin Fresh Yeast Bread Mix
  - Incredible Crescents, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0112)
    Product: Crescent rolls
    Note: Tradition, Color photographs on cover and inside, recipes
  - Quaker Oats Wholegrain Cookbook, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0113)
    Note: Cover: wholegrain oats
  - Quaker Oats Wholegrain Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0114)
    Note: Cover: prepared dishes
  - Bran Chex plan for good cooking, 1983 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0115)
  - Favorite Recipes: Light and Easy: Armour Lower Salt, 1989 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0116)
    Company: Armour Food Company
    Product: Armour Lower Salt Ham, Armour Lower Salt Cheddar Cheese, etc.
    Note: Health: high blood pressure, diet, nutrition. Spokesperson: Armand E. Brodeur, MD.
  - Magic Can, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0117)
  - Beef Is a Microwave Favorite, 1988 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0118)
  - Light Cooking with Beef, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0119)
    Company: California Beef Council
  - Foie Gras de France: Summit of Gastronomy, 1981 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0120)
    Company: Foie Gras de France
    Product: French foods mostly meat
    Note: French product, published in USA. Luxury food
  - When It Comes to Great Chicken, Holly Farms Wrote the Book, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0121)
    Company: Holly Farms Poultry Industries, Inc.
    Note: Leaflet contains recipe from, advertisement for 'Complete Chicken Cookbook' and coupons
  - Why America Comes Home to Holly Farms: A Guide to Fresh Chicken And Fresh Chicken Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0122)
    Note: Pamphlet, How to handle and prepare fresh chicken
  - The Turkey Store Cookbook, 1983 (Box 1980s-04, Item 1980s-0123)
    Company: Jerome Foods, Inc.
    Product: Turkey Store turkey meat
    Note: Color photographs, some black-and-white drawings, enclosed letter from Mary Schaffhausen, retail product manager
  - How Did You Fix Something So Fantastic So Fast?' Recipes with Lamb, 1980 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0124)
    Company: Lamb Education Center
    Note: black-and-white drawings (mainly small icons), introduction, cooking with frozen lamb
  - Pork Cooking with Time in Mind, 1986 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0125)
    Note: Color photographs, diagram of parts of pig, nutrition facts, refrigerator and freezer times
  - Cooking Today's Pork, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0126)
    Note: Scientifically raised pigs produce new kind of pork. Health, nutrition
  - Omaha Steaks Cookbook: Vol. 17, 1987 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0127)
    Note: Includes Food for Thought facts, Introduction with James A. Beard, steak cooking chart
  - Good Life Guide and Cookbook, 1989 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0128)
    Note: spokesperson Jana Applely
  - All Seasons All Reasons Cookbook, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0129)
    Product: Underwood
  - No Fuss Chicken, 1982 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0130)
    Product: Swanson Chunk Chicken Products
    Note: Health, nutrition, weight
  - No Fuss Chicken, 1982 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0131)
  - Butterball Holiday Turkey Recipes, 1982 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0132)
    Company: Swift-Eckrich, Inc.
    Product: Butterball turkey
    Note: Color photographs, cooking guide
  - Wilson Family Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0133)
  - Better Homes and Gardens Best Wok recipes, Compliments of West Bend, 1985 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0134)
    Product: Multiple incl. Karo corn syrup
    Note: Some color photographs, cookbook offer
  - Calcium Tips & Recipes, 1986 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0135)
    Company: Canada Safeway
    Product: Safeway grocery store
  - No Bones About it – Osteoporosis is Serious Business (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0136)
    Product: Safeway grocery store, milk
  - Wok Master Home Style Chinese Cooking, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0137)
    Company: Fairsound Corporation
    Note: Some black-and-white drawings and symbols, introduction, how to hold chopsticks
  - New Birdseye Super Suppers, 1980 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0138)
    Product: Birds Eye vegetables
    Note: Spiral bound, color photographs
  - Betty Crocker: Out of the Orient, 1987 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0139)
    Product: Betty Crocker products
    Note: Exotic' foods, some cultural information on 'Oriental' nations
  - Shopping $ense For Seniors, 1981 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0140)
    Product: Giant food stores
  - Great Dinners Outdoors from Gulf Lite, 1982 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0141)
    Product: Gulf Lite
  - What's Cookin' Canada?, 1985 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0142)
    Company: Strategium Medium Inc.
    Product: Florelle, Melitta, Old Dutch, Gulf, Reddi-wip, Schneiders, Wardair
    Note: Canadian airlines
  - International Favorites from Kikkoman, Bertolli, and ReaLemon, 1989 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0143)
    Company: Multiple--Kikkoman, Borden Inc., Bertolli USA
    Product: Kikkoman sauces, ReaLemon juice, Bertolli olive oil
    Note: Color photographs, sections separated by product
  - Kroger nutrition news Volume LI: Bananas – Strange Fruit with a bunch of nutrition, 1984 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0144)
    Product: Grocery store, Bananas
  - Round-The-Clock-Creations, 1989 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0145)
    Product: Multiple Nabisco products
    Note: Color photographs, coupons in back
  - Holiday Cookies, Sweets, Appetizers, and Meals, 1986 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0146)
    Note: Color photographs, Cookie tips, nutritional information, Cookbook special offer
  - Come For Dinner, 1984 (Box 1980s-05, Item 1980s-0147)
    Note: Color photographs, timetable, nutritional information, beverage suggestions
  - Stay Trim Quick Diet Recipes, 1988 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0148)
    Company: Plough, Inc.
    Product: Stay Trim and multiple products
    Note: Color photographs, How to Lose Weight section, Stay Trim mints and gum
  - The Spicy Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0149)
    Product: Multiple products (spices)
    Note: Free with Listerine purchase, black-and-white drawings, information on each spice, including storage
  - Little Imagination and Stouffers, 1981 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0150)
    Company: Stouffer Foods Corporation
    Product: Stouffers products
    Note: Creativity, ease of preparation, efficiency
  - Nopales, 1987 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0151)
    Company: Try-Foods International, Inc.
    Product: Kroger, nopales
  - Sopate, 1987 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0152)
    Product: Kroger, sopate
  - 59 fabulous recipes for your genuine Weber Kettle. Easy to follow, fun to use…, 1980 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0153)
    Product: Weber Kettle (grill)
  - Soup'er Tuna Cookbook, 1980 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0154)
    Company: Campbell Soup Company, Van Camp Sea Food Company, Du Pont de Nemours & Company, Inc.
    Product: Campbell's soups, Chicken of the Sea tuna, SilverStone and Teflon pans
    Note: A cookbook for the Eighties' offering 'value, nutrition, and convenience'
  - Conimex-- Deliciously different/Remarkably Oriental, 1980 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0155)
    Company: Conimex
    Product: Chinese/Indonesian foods, various
  - Conimex – your home guide to authentic oriental cuisine, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0156)
  - 3 in 1 Breezy Recipes for Picnics, Cookouts, Buffets, 1985 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0157)
    Product: Del Monte, Ortega, A.1, Moton, Hawaiian Punch, Chun King, and Grey Poupon brands
  - General Foods Trademark Recipes, 1982 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0158)
  - Baking Festival Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0159)
    Note: Illustrations of children
  - Treasury of Sweet Treats: Confections Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0160)
    Product: Miracle Whip, Kraft foods, Parkay margarine, Philadelphia cream cheese, etc.
    Note: Spokesperson: Dorothy Holland. Brief history of innovations in the field of candy and sweet baking
  - Salad Source (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0161)
    Product: Catalina, Miracle Whip, Kraft salad dressings/mayonnaise, Philadelphia cream cheese
  - Salads From Beginning to Endive, 1980 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0162)
    Product: Kraft salad dressings/cheese, Parkay margarine, Miracle Whip, Philadelphia cream cheese
  - Bright Ideas for the Holidays from Kraft General Foods, 1989 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0163)
    Company: Kraft General Foods, Inc.
    Product: Birds Eye frozen produce, Kraft cheeses, Cheez Whiz, Pillsbury dinner rolls, Parkay margarine, Velveeta cheese products, Good Seasons dressings, etc.
  - Bar-B-Q Basics, 1981 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0164)
    Company: McCormick-Schilling spices, Kikkoman sauces, Miller beer, Western Iceberg Lettuce, Charmglow gas barbeques
  - America's 30th Bake-off Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0165)
    Note: Includes...ethnic and economy entries.' Nutrition information
  - Festive Holiday Recipes, 1981 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0166)
    Product: Pillsbury's Best Flour, etc.
    Note: Christmas theme. Family traditions
  - Harvest Time Pies, 1984 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0167)
    Product: Pillsbury All Ready Pie Crusts, Pillsbury's Best Flour, etc.
    Note: Tradition: American farmer motif
  - Low Calorie Cookbook: A guide to Family Weight Control, 1980 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0168)
    Product: Green Giant Pillsbury brand products
    Note: Weight: includes calorie guide and nutrition information
  - Say Yes to Less Cookbook: Less sugar, less salt, less fat, 1983 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0169)
    Product: Green Giant, Pillsbury Sprinkle Sweet Food Sweetener and other Pillsbury products
    Note: Health food, control of weight--more health-related than appearance
  - Summertime Favorite Recipes, 1981 (Box 1980s-06, Item 1980s-0170)
    Note: Summer theme. Economy and creativity
  - Bake It Special!, 1979 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0171)
    Note: Tradition: 'Combined old-fashioned, good flavor with today's convenience' includes coupons
  - Bake-Off and other favorites Treasury, 1989 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0172)
    Product: Hungry Jack, Green Giant, and Pillsbury brand products
    Note: Recipes and nutritional information for apps., bread, entres, desserts
  - Calorie Counter Recipe Book, 1981 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0173)
    Product: Green Giant and Pillsbury brand products
    Note: Includes Pillsbury's 'Sprinkle Sweet' and 'Sweet-10'sugar replacements, 'Figurines' diet snack
  - Children's Choice Cookbook, 1982 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0174)
    Note: Snacks for children
  - Chocolate Lover's Cookbook, 1983 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0175)
    Product: Pillsbury Chocolate Cake Mix, etc.
    Note: Spokesperson: Renee Dignan
  - Cookies, Cookies and More Cookies Cookbook, Volume 2, 1982 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0176)
  - Great Summer Get-together Recipes, 1982 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0177)
    Product: Hungry Jack, Green Giant foods, Pillsbury's Best Flour, etc.
    Note: Summer theme: Events and parties
  - Harvest Time Cook Book, 1980 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0178)
  - Hearty Main Dishes: Save Time --Save Money, 1982 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0179)
  - International Favorites, 1983 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0180)
    Note: Multicultural, international foods, ease of preparation, creativity of foods
  - Menus Made Simple Cookbook: Easy on the budget, easy on the cook, 1981 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0181)
    Note: Economy, nutrition. Seasonal
  - Summertime Across America Cookbook, 1983 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0182)
    Product: Pillsbury flours and mixes, Hungry Jack products, Green Giant products
  - Fiesta Style!, 1989 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0183)
    Company: Rosarita
    Product: Mexican foods, various
    Note: Includes coupons
  - New Treasury of Almond Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0184)
    Product: Blue Diamond Almond products
    Note: Nutrition, ease of preparation
  - Crazy About Almonds and Chocolate Cookbook, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0185)
    Company: Almond Board
    Note: Color photographs and drawings, some black-and-white drawings, things every good cook should know about almonds and chocolate
  - Diamond Walnut Recipe Gems, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0186)
  - Diamond Walnut Cookie Favorites, 1984 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0187)
  - Microwave Magic: Recipes Form Your Oklahoma Peanut Commission, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0188)
  - Blue Bonnet Presents Colonial American Recipes, circa 1980s (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0189)
  - 101 Cooking Tips & Other Tricks with Pam, 1984 (Box 1980s-07, Item 1980s-0190)
    Company: Boyle-Midway
    Product: Pam No-Stick Cooking Spray
  - Parkay Margarine Cookbook, 1980 (Box 1980s-08, Item 1980s-0191)
  - Great Cooking with Butter Flavor Crisco, 1982 (Box 1980s-08, Item 1980s-0192)
    Note: Introduction by Beverly Nye (includes photograph of her inside back cover)